Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Writings and Speeches, 1912-2000 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Open Files, 1912-1993 and undated
  - Watson, John Broadus
    - 1920. Article. Conditioned Emotional Reactions. Journal of Experimental Psychology, Feb. (Box 50)
    - 1921. Article. How to Break Down Resistance to Life Insurance. Insurance Field, Nov. 25 (Box 50)
    - 1922. Article. Can Science Determine Your Baby's Career Before It Can Talk? New York American Sunday Magazine, Jan. 8 (Box 50)
    - 1923. Article. Gigantic Industry that Needs Advertising's Help. Printers Ink, Apr. 5 (Box 50)
    - 1926. Article. What is Behaviorism? Harpers Magazine, May (Box 50)
    - 1928. Article. Feed Me on Facts. Saturday Review of Literature, June 16 (Box 50)
    - 1935. Speech. Influencing the Mind of Another (Box 50)
  - Wax, Ed
    - 1993. Speech. From Demarketing to Trust Marketing: A Brand Relationship Approach to Marketing (Box 50)
  - Weekes, Alan
    - 1958. Speech. Creative Thinking in Advertising (Box 50)
  - Weilbacher, William M.
    - 1967. Speech. What Happens to Advertisements when They Grow Up? (Box 50)
    - 1969. Speech. Market Research Contribution to Marketing Planning (Box 50)
    - 1969. Speech. Thoughts about the area of Dominant Influence (Box 50)
  - Weinrich, Len
    - 1984. Speech. Pan-European Advertising (Box 50)
  - Weist, Ward
    - 1979. Other writing. Reminiscences (draft) (Box 50)
  - Welty, Robert
    - 1969. Speech. Advertising Salesman and the Computer (Box 50)
  - Whiteside, H. O.
    - 1958. Speech. Symbols for Sale (Box 50)
    - 1961. Speech. Social Trends in a Changing World (Box 50)
    - 1961. Speech. Why Research is of No Help to Marketing (Box 50)
  - Wierum, Thorn
    - 1974-1987. Other writing. Memoranda and miscellaneous (Box 50)
  - Wilgar, Steve
    - 1979. Speech. How to Improve the Return on Your Advertising Investment (Box 50)
    - 1984. Speech. Defending the Brand Management System (Box 50)
    - 1984. Other writing. Responses to brand management talk (Box 50)
  - Willem, John M.
    - 1955. Speech. What Will You Sell to Whom? (Box 50)
    - 1958. Article. Interurbia is Here to Stay (Box 50)
  - Wilson, Edward B. (Ted)
    - 1974. Article. Outlook for the Advertising Agency Business in the United States for 1974 (Box 50)
  - Wilson, Edward G., (2 folders)
    - 1962. Speech. Will LAFTA be Another EEC? (Box 50)
    - 1962. Speech. Talk to Sydney Office staff (Box 50)
    - 1963. Speech. Talk to Representatives (Box 50)
    - 1967. Speech. Montreal ICC Congress (2 versions) (Box 50)
    - 1969. Speech. Learning is Beautiful: Preliminary Objectives of Talk at Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges (see also Peter Gilow Papers) (Box 50)
    - 1971. Speech. Advertising and the Government (Box 50)
    - 1971. Other writing. Where is Advertising going? (notes) (Box 50)
    - 1974. Article. Outlook for the Advertising Agency Business in the United States for 1974 (Box 50)
    - 1975. Speech. Let Me Do It (Box 50)
    - 1975. Other writing. Transition at JWT (book chapter draft) (Box 50)
    - 1976. Speech. Security Analysts Meeting (Box 50)
    - 1980. Speech. Presentation to Cali's Honors History Class (Box 50)
    - 1984. Speech. Talk to JWT Operations Committee (Box 50)
    - 1985. Speech. Speech to Retired Directors Dinner (speech and notes) (Box 50)
    - 1986. Speech. Directors' Dinner (notes for speech) (Box 50)
  - Wilt, George
    - 1973. Article. 4A Newspaper Committee Urges Support of Ad Reps. Editor and Publisher, Oct. 13 (Box 50)
  - Wilt, Harold
    - 1956. Speech. Media Evaluation (Box 50)
  - Winick, Charles
    - 1974. Other writing. Major Concepts of Behavioral Science Applicable to Marketing Research (conference paper) (Box 50)
  - Woolf, James D., (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - 1926. Other writing. Breaking Into Advertising as a Vocation (pamphlet) (Box 51)
    - 1948. Article. Salesense in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1950. Article. Heart Appeal in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Advertising at its Finest is a Servant of the People (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Advertising Czar? Perish the Thought! (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Advertising is Not So Difficult as It is Often Made to Appear (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Advertising...the Least Effective of All the Activities of Man (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Advice to America's Thousands of Panless Advertisers (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Come Right Out and Say What You Mean (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Difficult Art of Researching Human Handerkins (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Fading Away of Good Taste in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Failure to Quote Prices is a Disservice to the Public (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Hardest Working Fellow in the Agency Business (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Hark Ye to the Voice of the People (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. How Allergic are We to Facts about What We Get for Our Money? (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Is It Fair to Pre-empt a Common Product Virtue? (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Is It Possible for Agencies to Have a Continuing Corporate Experience? (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Is It True That Women are Denied the Bigger Opportunities in Advertising? (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Is the Customer Simple Minded? (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Is the Public Developing a Tolerance for Absurd Human Behavior in Ads? (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. It is Wise to Put a Feeling of 'Nice People' Into Your Copy (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. It Isn't Size that Puts Pull in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. It Takes a Long, Long, Long Time to Make an Idea Sink in (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Look for Potent Ideas by Studying Inadequacies of Mankind (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Mail Order Pot O' Gold (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Myth about Salesmen (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. No Researcher Has Yet Licked the Problem of Human Vanity (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. No Sale is Ever Made Until a Buyer Believes in the Integrity of a Seller (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Positive or Negative Appeal? are There Any Rules to Guide Us? (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Promise of Psychological Satisfaction Might Be a Better Way to Sell Tea (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Salesense in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Seems That a Few Food Writers Still aren't Hip to the Facts of Life (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Selective Appeal in Definitive Market is Sometimes a Good Strategy (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Testimonials Make Most Salesense when They are Authoritative and Credible (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. There's Sales Persuasion in the Everybody's Doing It Idea (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. Too Much Vacuity in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1951. Article. What is a good Advertising Idea? (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. $64 Question in Direct Mail Selling (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. About Insurance Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Advertising Business is No Sacred Cow to Me (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Advertising Failures are Often Due to Shortcomings of the Product (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Advertising-Like Pollstering is a Baffling Business (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Advice to Beginners on How to Be Really Good in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Another Question about Which There is No Agreement Among the Experts (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Are Both Right, Both Wrong, or What? (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Are Excesses of Advertising Accepted with 'Amused Tolerance'? (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Are National Advertising Agencies a Must for National Advertisers? (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Business Papers Must Be Spearhead the Drive for Better Trade Publication Copy (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. C Stands for Cat-Unless You Prefer Obfuscation (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Concerning Futility and Wastefulness of the Indirect Approach (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Congratulations, 'Fortune,' on Your Attack on Ad-iness (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Copywriters Play It Safe when They assume Retail Salesmanship is a Myth (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Don't Sell So Hard that You Forget to Be Friendly (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Factory Facts about Your Product Often Make Weak Copy (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Five Reasons Why Small Ads Will Pay Off for You (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Here's an Object Lesson for Advertisers of Phony Bargain Sales (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Is Most Good Advertising NEWS for the Direct Opposite? (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Is the 15% commission System Jeopardizing Agencies' No. 1 Job? (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. It Takes a Long Time for a Bona Fide Idea Man to Fade Away (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. It's Ideas--Not Tricky Typography--That Capture and Hold Reader Interest (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. It's Still Salesmanship in Print, Even when the Results are 'Indirect' (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Magic X in Copywriting is Not Taught in College Classrooms (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. My Last Word on Short vs. Long Copy (Box 51)
    - 1952. Other writing. Notes Taken at a JWT Copy Clinic (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Perhaps for Effectiveness We Should Drop Superlatives Altogether (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Perhaps It's a Kindergarten Question, But Do You Know the Answer? (2 versions) (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Perhaps the Perfect Advertisement is an Artful Blend of Algebra and Music (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Pictures are Potent but Don't Forget the Power of Words (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Rankest Nonsense I've Ever Hard about Copywriting (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Rarely Indeed Do We See Notable Prose from an Adman's Pen (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Remember the Most Interesting Subject n the World (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Some Suggestions on What to Do in an Advertising Rat Race (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Take Time to Think (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Testing of Copy Appeals and Techniques in Still in its Infancy (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. There are Food-Copy Adjectives that No Longer Make Mouths Water (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. There's a Vast Difference for Improvement in Retail Newspaper Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Today the Consumer's Most Want Item of Information is Price (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Try to Make Your Copy Consistent with Ordinary Human Experience (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. We Admen, Says a Well-Known Copy Chief, are a Bunch of Copycats (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. Weeds Still Flourish in Adlan's Gardens (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. What Counts is Not the Size of the Space but the Size of the Selling Idea (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. What is Caviar for the Goose May Be Pig's Kuckles for the Gander (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. What is Wrong with Corn in Advertising? (Box 51)
    - 1952. Article. You're Sitting Pretty when You Have a Reputation for Integrity (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Adult Salesmanship-in-Print Pays Off for Some Oil Companies (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Advertising Cannot Make S______ Purses Out of Sow's Ears (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Advertising is in Part a Delayed-Action Time Bomb (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Advertising Seldom Succeeds Notably in Combating the 'Thing to Do' (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Be Your Own Guinea Pig in Your Studies of Human Behavior (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Concerning One of the Most Fundamental Principles in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Concerning the Difficult Problem of Being Believed in Copy (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Copy Hits a New Low as a Fearful Bore (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Demonstrate... (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Dinner at Home With Rhonda Flemming (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Don't Underrate the Power of Artful Word-Slinging (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Does Your Copy Need More Why for Greater Credibility? (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Good Sportsmanship Key Requirement of Money-Back Guarantees (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. How Vividly are They Remembering Your Promise at the Moment of Purchase? (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. I'm Getting a Little Board With the Old Masters (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. It's Risky to Count on Advertising's Forcing Distribution (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Let's Not Cry 'Woolf' about Oil Company Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Man Shall Not Live By Bread Alone (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Mediocrity, Thy Name is Oil Company Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. New American Leisure is Good for Business (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Observations on an Interesting Suggestion by Zenith's President (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Problem Well Stated is a Problem Half Solved (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Question that Splits the Advertising Fraternity Right Down the Middle (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Retail Advertising Should Sell Ideas as Well as Bargain Prices (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Salute to the Artdirecting Adman! (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Sanctimonious Cigarette Hucksters (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Some Notable Exceptions to the Mediocrity of Oil Company Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Something Extra' Multiplies the Power of Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. Son, Your Head Omits the Guts of the Story' (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. There is No Cheap Way to Buy and Hold Consumer Favor (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. There is Persuasiveness in Bashful Sincerity and Comely Love (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. What are the Basic Laws on This Question (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. What in the World is Advertising Coming To! (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. What Shall I Serve My Family for Dinner Tonight? (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. What Should Your Package Label Be--a Poster or a Page Advertisement? (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. You, Too, Can Make a Martini Your Guests Will Rave About! (Box 51)
    - 1953. Article. You've Got to Use the Bait They're Hankering' for (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Actual Sales Test is the Only Sure Method of Copy Research (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Advertising Can Sell Only Some of the People Some of the Time (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Advertising's Greatest Weakness is its Glaring Lack of Credibility (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Appraise Your Advertisements in Terms of All-Over Impact (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Are you in Step with Ever-Changing Consumer Wants? (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. As for Me, Mom, I Want My Gerber's (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Big Boast Does Not Develop and Nurture Brand Loyalty (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Big Promises Not Always Realizable (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Borg-Warner Ripley Campaign Pays Off (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Bromides Discourage Readership (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Busy Stage Sets Can Murder Dancers...and Ideas (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. But How Were Thousands of Motorists to Be Convinced? (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Concerning TV Commercials and the Most Interesting Subject in the World (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Copywriters Can Learn Much from Study of Mail Selling Techniques (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Credible Promises Require Little Proof (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Discover What You Think Before You Write (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Does the Big Idea Come through Sharp and Clear? (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Do Recipes Contribute to the Effectiveness of Food Advertising? (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Effective Headlines Do Not Always Spell Out a Promised Benefit (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Flavor-Appeal of First Importance in Food Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. I Have Little Faith in the Statistical Man (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. I Have Yet to Meet a Bona Fide Advertising Authority (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. If Your Product is Saleable It is Not Dull to Everybody (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Is the Public Becoming Immune to Your 'Battering?' (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. It Seems that the 'Bear' Facts Can Be Beautiful (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Money-One of the Most Engrossing Preoccupations of Man (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Not Everybody Likes His Toast Well Done (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Off-Brand, as Well as Off-List Selling is a Problem (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Outstanding Ideas are Rarely the Product of 'Committee Thinking' (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Partial Readership is of Supermen Importance (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. People are Not Always More Interesting than Things (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Readership Research Does Not Support Freak Attention-Getters (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Selling Power--True Measure of Great Advertisements (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Separate Promotions More Effective than 'Umbrella' Campaign (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Settle Your Basic IDEA Before You Think about Pictures (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Some Thoughts Concerning the Good Old Snob Appeal (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. Specific Facts about Specific Policies Might Strengthen Insurance Company (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. There are Times when the Negative Appeal Makes Good Sense (Box 51)
    - 1954. Article. What You Say Often More Important than How You Say It (Box 51)
    - 1954-1955. Article. Advertising Agencies Pick Their Best of (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Advertising Agencies Pick the Best of (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. All Media are Instruments of Salesmanship (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Advertising Should Create Brand Name Familiarity (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Basic Philosophy of Good Advertising Remains (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Brand Familiarity Alone a Great Sale asset (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Combat Consumer's Forgetfulness with Point of Sale Remindership (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Continued Repetition of the Same Advertisement (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Good Sales are No Proof that Nonsensical Advertising Pay (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Emotional--or Reason Why? (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. How Significant are the Readership Ratings? (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Irate Housewife is Repelled by Sameness in Advertising (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Popular Notions are Stubborn Things (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. Simpler the Ad, the Greater its Impact (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. What Sells Groceries is Eating Pleasure (Box 51)
    - 1955. Article. What Women Think about when They Turn to a Food. Article. (Box 51)
    - 1956. Article. Adopt an Individuality and Stay With It (Box 51)
    - 1956. Article. Creative Genius is No Gift of the Gods (Box 51)
    - 1956. Article. New Look in Grocery Store Ads (Box 51)
    - 1956. Article. Supermarket Dares to Be Different (Box 51)
    - 1956. Article. There's a Reason for Every Buying Action (Box 51)
    - Undated. Other writing. Some Random Notes on Trademarks and Tradenames (Box 51)
    - Undated. Other writing. James D. Woolf Talks... (draft of book) (Box 51)
  - Woolf, Janet
    - 1958. Article. What, If Anything, Does It Mean to Copy Writer? (Box 51)
    - 1959. Article. New Directors in Marketing: Answering Woman's Hunger for Information (Box 51)
    - 1959. Article. Today's Woman-And Premiums (Box 51)
    - 1960. Speech. Communicating With Women (Box 51)
  - Wright, William P. Jr.
    - 1956. Article. Urges Use of Proven Motivation Principles for Successful Promotion (Box 51)
    - 1957. Speech. Minimum Care Fabrics (Box 51)
  - Yeates, Allan B.
    - 1978. Speech. Advertising at the Crossroads (Box 51)
  - Yoder, Ken
    - 1987. Speech. Sales meeting (Box 51)
  - Young, James Webb, (1-8 of 11 folders) (Box 52)
    - 1921. Other writing. Control of the Advertising Agency (draft) (Box 52)
    - 1921. Article. Control of the Advertising Appropriation (Box 52)
    - 1925. Article. Words, Co-Partner With Value (Box 52)
    - 1927. Speech. What Do These Advertising Agencies Do for Their Commission? (Box 52)
    - 1933. Article. Advertising Agency Compensation Relation to Total Cost of Advertising (2 versions) (Box 52)
    - 1934. Article. Mr. Hill's Notes on Advertising Lectures (Box 52)
    - 1934. Other writing. Lectures by James Young (2 copies) (Box 52)
    - 1935. Article. Professor Looks at Advertising (Box 52)
    - 1941. Speech. What Shall We Do about It? (Box 52)
    - 1942. Article. Role of Management in Relation to Consumer Satisfaction (Box 52)
    - 1943. Article. Advertising as a New Technique for Management (Box 52)
    - 1945. Speech. What Advertising Learned from the War (Box 52)
    - 1946. Speech. Advertising Council at Work (Box 52)
    - 1946. Speech. Mechanism for Business Leadership (Box 52)
    - 1946. Article. Say It With Coupons (Box 52)
    - 1946. Speech. Wanted: More Free Enterprise--And Less Talk about It (Box 52)
    - 1947. Speech. Calling All Publication Salesmen (Box 52)
    - 1948. Speech. Speech to Advertising Council, Inc. (Box 52)
    - 1952. Speech. Are We Selling Americans short? (2 versions) (Box 52)
    - 1953. Article. Sale I Never Forgot (Box 52)
    - 1953. Article. Complete Angler (Box 52)
    - 1953. Article. Pervasive Art (Box 52)
    - 1953. Article. Technique for Producing Ideas (book excerpt) (Box 52)
    - 1954. Article. Advertising's Balance Sheet: on One Side, Instrument of Plenty; on the Other, 'Copywriter Strain' (Box 52)
    - 1954. Speech. My Advertising Ego- Biography (Box 52)
    - 1954. Speech. Nature of Advertising Knowledge (3 versions) (Box 52)
    - 1955. Other writing. What the J. Walter company Stands for (statement, 2 versions) (Box 52)
    - 1959. Speech. How to Make Life Most Interesting (Box 52)
    - 1959. Speech. Mirror for a Lady (2 versions) (Box 52)
    - 1960. Article. Changing Advertising Symbol (Box 52)
    - 1960. Speech. Five Uses of Advertising (Box 52)
    - 1960. Article. Found: A Responsible Critic of Advertising (Box 52)
    - 1960. Speech. How to Become an Advertising Man (3 versions) (Box 52)
    - 1960. Article. Open Letter to a Foundation (Box 52)
    - 1960. Speech. Some Footnotes to Famous Headlines (Box 52)
    - 1960. Article. Wanted: Responsible Advertising Critics (Box 52)
    - 1961. Article. Advertising Agency Paradox (Box 52)
    - 1961. Speech. Agency Compensation Paradox (Box 52)
    - 1961. Article. Do We Need a College of Propaganda (Box 52)
    - 1961. Article. Jim Webb Young on Toynbee (Box 52)
    - 1961. Article. What's Behind the 15% Ad Fee (Box 52)
  - Young, James Webb (continued), (9-11 of 11 folders) (Box 53)
    - 1962. Other writing. How to Become an Advertising Man (book) (Box 53)
    - 1962. Article. Jim Young Reviews (column) (Box 53)
    - 1963. Article. Jim Young Reviews (column) (Box 53)
    - 1963-1964. Article. Jim Young Reviews (column) (Box 53)
    - 1964. Article. Mister J. Walter Thompson (Box 53)
    - 1965. Article. Best $10 Investment (Box 53)
    - Undated. Speech. Speech to Youngsters Interested in a Career in Advertising (Box 53)
  - Yuspeh, Sonia, (8 folders)
    - 1975. Other writing. Changeable Consumer (research report) (Box 53)
    - 1975. Article. Diagnosis--The Handmaiden of Prediction (Box 53)
    - 1976. Article. Forget the Product Life Cycle (Box 53)
    - 1976. Speech. What's Happening to Social Values (Box 53)
    - 1977. Speech. Product Life Cycle (Box 53)
    - 1977. Speech. TV Violence from the Viewers Vantage (Box 53)
    - 1979. Speech. Brand Utility Yardstick (Box 53)
    - 1979. Article. Medium Versus the Message (speech and article) (Box 53)
    - 1979. Article. On-the-air Test Scores May Not Be Telling All (Box 53)
    - 1980. Speech. On What It Takes to Be a Top Flight Agency Researcher (Box 53)
    - 1981. Speech. Branded Products at the Crossroads (Box 53)
    - 1981. Speech. Confident Ones: A Review of the Campaign Evaluation Methods Used by EFFIE entrants (Box 53)
    - 1981. Article. Recall Debate (Box 53)
    - 1982. Article. Can Segments Be Born Again? Journal of Advertising Research, June/July (Box 53)
    - 1982. Speech. Turbulent Times for Branded Products (2 versions) (Box 53)